we are the top three life insurer in the
Philippines top in just 10 years time
who is FWD and why you have to choose us
let me tell you more about our company
FWD FWD started in 2013 operating its
first business in Hong Kong Macau and
Thailand an S screen 2014 they decided
to invest in the Philippines kayar FWD
life insurance Philippines in a matter
of 10 years FW D is now operating in 10
markets in Asia and has more than 11
million customers wow today FWD is in
the top five in Southeast Asia for new
business sales and is managing 58.9
billion in total assets at in the
Philippines based on blackbox Research
FWD Philippines takes pride in being the
most different brand and for landing the
number two spot for being Innovative and
customer Centric to in Testament that
FWD is committed to our vision our
vision is to change the way people feel
about insurance we are not an ordinary
insurance company Al that's not all here
in FWD we also encourage our planners
not only to be productive but to look
out for their personal and professional
development mdrt or million doll
Roundtable
member mdrt MD RT it is
something life insurance it's a global
independent Association of the world's
leading Life Insurance and financial
services professionals so every year 2%
qualify mdrt or million doll Round Table
member and we are blessed and I'm proud
to say that SI FWD as a group ranks
number six amongst multinational
companies around the globe in terms of
mdrt membership while FWD Philip
is rank number two for MD
membership MD artist and I'm proud to
say scre we are the top three life
insurer in the Philippines so just a
short period of time
years in terms of ranking business
annual premium equivalent
in just 10 years
time and we ended 2023 with 10,000
financial planners but as of today we
are currently at 18,000 and good
news FWD it's a two-in-one app that
helps you achieve real life goals and
manage your policy at the same time in
just one
to and if you want to know more about
products like life insurance product
health insurance with money back
guarantee investment retir education
planning or estate planning or Company
Insurance just message me and I'll be
very glad to assist you my name is picha
bashal I'm a branch manager here in FWD
I do videos about insurance and personal
finance follow me if you'd like this
kind of content